Hello everyone! This is Amonoko Noah and Alice Yamano of New Ally Call Joy!
So this time, Alice and I are here to visit Choa Onni, where you can wear a lot of Korean uniforms!
We are here at Choa Onni, where you can wear a lot of Korean uniforms!
Today, we're going to choose from a variety of uniforms and take a lot of pictures together.
So please take a look until the end!
So let's go choose!
I'd like to choose one!
There are so many to choose from.
I think we're going to go with
We have our eyes on this mustard joy color
I've got my eye on this mustard joy color.
How can I show you this?
This pastel color
Can you see them?
We're considering these two colors.
We need to decide on a combination.
That's for sure.
There's the bottom one, too.
There's a lot to choose from.
Let's start with this one.
This one...
I'll go with the mustard joy color.
Here you go.
Let's take it off.
Got it.
Yes!
Very nice!
Wow!
I'll see you in a bit.
Ta-da!
Oh! So cute!
Now, let's have a look at the girls.
I'd like to choose one.
I like the gray one
I like the gray one.
I like it.
Handmade.
Something like this.
Oh, wow.
You're right.
Okay, now we're done.
Like this
I'd like to continue.
Inside.
Yes, inside, too.
I heard there's a resto.
I think it's a little bit hard to be Alice.
I think it's hard to be Alice.
Oh, it's nice.
It's nice.
Looks good in black
Shall I try it in black?
It's nice.
Thank you.
Okay, let's do this one.
We'll go with this one.
Let's change.
Let's get changed.
Let's get changed! Let's get changed!
Getting dressed
Okay, let's go.
Please do.
Ta-da!
So cute!
Hello!
What do you think?
It looks great on you.
Oh! The ribbon is so cute.
Thank you!
I'm looking forward to seeing you too, Ayu.
Have you changed, Alice?
Yes, I did.
I'll take care of it.
Oh!
It's cute.
The ribbon is so big and cute.
Yes, it is.
Cute.
It looks good on you. It's a good look.
Thank you.Thank you.
Okay, well, we'll get right to the pictures.
Let's take a picture.
Yes, sir!
So cute.
You look like someone who's caught something.
Thank you.
He's cute.
He compliments me all the time.
You're adorable.
Yes, yes, he always remembers me.
Oh!
Here's the train.
Suspension straps.
I'm wearing straps.
Oh, man.
It's so cool!
Oh, wow.
Can we get in here with just the two of us?
Can we both get in?
Is the angle okay?
Here we go.
Let's do it sling style.
I love it! This is very nice.
It's looking good.
I got it.
Thank you very much.
Now we'd like to choose the second dress.
Okay, let's choose.
Next...
I'd like to go to Mr. Aster.
Do you have a favorite color?
Hmmm...
I like this one, too.
That's cute.
Which one are you going for?
Uh...
This pink one is nice, but the light blue one is cute too.
That's for sure.
Alice, the light blue one's nice.
I think pink and light blue is cute.
I do.
Hmm? Oh! Wow!
Cute!
That's what it looked like.
Yes, it's insect style.
This is an insect, too.
The light blue one looks like this.
Oh!
Cute!
Nice!
What do you think would look good underneath?
I think it should be pretty bright.
Yeah, I think so.
I like it here.
I think this is good.
I think it's good.
You want this one? Are you sure?
Yes, it's good!
Okay, I'll go with this one in pink and light blue.
It's decided!
Now, let's get changed here!
I'm changing.
I think I'll get out of the ribbon kimono.
Okay, I'll get out.
What do you think?
I love the ribbons.
It's pretty, isn't it?
Ponchos.
Different colors.
What do you think?
And the buttons are cute.
The fact that she was wearing ribbons...
A little bit of power.
I think it's cute.
It's very cute.
The ribbons are a nice touch.
Just the two of us.Just the two of us.
What's it like?
Come on.
Come sit down.
Here we go.
Here we go, Mr. Squirrel.
There you go.
It's got carrots on it.
Try it on.
Worried about looking like a crab.
Crab, your eyes are a little bit heart-shaped. So, next, I'd like to take a purikura picture called "Insen Nekko.
We often go out to take purikura privately, but today is the first time for us to try this type of photo.
But today is the first time for us to try this type.
Let's do it.
What do you think? Isn't this a little intriguing?
I like this one.
Oh, wow.
Here's a wide batch.
I'm going with the rabbit.
I like the way you count.
Oh, great.
I'll go with the second one.
I'm going with the top!
That's great!
That's it!
I got it.
That's great!
Here it comes.
It's coming out.
That's great.
Well, I've seen it.
It's so cute.
Cute and full of bunnies!
Rabbits.
Cute
Yes, that's what I'm talking about.
This time, I wore a Korean uniform at Chua Onni
I took a picture with Alice.
How was Alice?
Well, we were happy that we could choose our own uniforms from scratch.
Thank you so much.
I also had a lot of fun with Alice choosing which uniforms to wear and taking pictures with her.
Thank you Alice.
Thank you very much for watching and taking pictures with Alice.
Thank you very much for watching this video.
Thank you very much for watching this episode.
That's all for now, this is Kona Amano and Alice Yamano from Mary Quarl Joy.
and Alice Yamano of Mary Quarrel Joy.
Bye bye!
This is Alice.